FWD not only offers Innovative products
but they also offer Financial
opportunities and business opportunities
for the Filipinos that include many
exciting perks they Empower people to
start their own business where they can
earn through sales by offering
Innovative products
[Music]
with your customers provided lahat the
FWD they want follow me HMO and extended
to your other families world-class
access to professional training so they
can Inspire and Empower their customers
and the best is work life balance is the
top priority they offer travel
incentives
travel Safari South Korea New York Japan
thank you
[Music]
foreign
about the future forget the past and
start enjoying the presence quotes
FWD life insurance
they want to help people feel confident
and focused on their lives living
without hesitations
they are also changing the way people
feel about insurance insurance
and what I also love about FWB insurance
is they also offer products that fits
your lifestyle and your needs kite
animals
questions there you can go guys to
fwd.com or contact an FWD financial
advisor so you can know more about FWB
life's Insurance exciting brand and
other Innovative products that they can
offer powder FWD life insurance social
media accounts their Facebook page at
fwdlife.ph their Instagram picked off
and Twitter at FWD life underscore
Phi description box and guys FWD not
only offers Innovative products but they
also offer Financial opportunities and
business opportunities for the Filipinos
that include many exciting products
through their agency and Bank Assurance
effort during the event in experience 18
Ambassador Chief partnership officer
about the perks of being a Financial
Solutions consultant
Ice Age from FWE Philippines Chief
partnership officer Miss Eileen
I'd like to Define you know the
financials
who are these people these are our FWD
employees who are assigned in all our
Security Bank branches uh Security Bank
has been our partner for almost 10 years
now and I've been having a great partner
number one is the competitive benefits
that have been one palangi HMO and
expanded Bayan to your other families
number two they are technology
Deliverance
[Music]
with your customers provided the FWD we
also have world-class access to
professional things so they can Inspire
and empowered customers premium travel
experience
for their exemplary performance
we also have the opportunity to
collaborate with the stakeholders due to
the growth of the company by helping
others celebrate leaving and also guys
miss adnel valessa the chief agency
officer of fwp Philippines explained
also as the benefits of the financial
advisors
of our company this afternoon allow me
to discuss anxiety and empowering
benefits that our financial advisors
enjoy to power up in offering easy to
understand and Best in Class products
for their clients or for our customers
report our CEO earlier and he said that
our 10 years in the market FWD started
10 years ago and I've been to the
availability for nine years and I have
seen how built the ecosystem from
scratch and then it also hurts since day
one we have been processing and issuing
his insurance policies digital end to
end and I think we're one of the very
few insurance companies in the
Philippines who have that track record
they treat their financial advisors as
business partners they Empower people to
start their own business where they can
earn through sales by offering
Innovative products like the FSC
financial advisors are also equipped
with technology
tablets and performance for transaction
with their client and also and agusto
enco is the winning level stops that we
offer inside business cards to parties
and they also have the high the elite
software in Singapore and other group
Office programs and the best is work
life balance is built up Priority in the
health like FFC if you can buy your
performance mode they offer travel
incentives
South Korea New York Japan
so if you want me talk to their
financial advisor or follow their social
social media accounts and how you can
apply as Financial Solutions consultant
and as a financial advisors we also
Empower their agents to grow a purposely
business where they can help others to
celebrate leaving their ultimate mission
is to grow the company big and fast
all right guys
let's go
[Music]
everybody here today
it's an immersive Journey that shows
fwd's commitment to changing the way
people feel about insurance who are
already insured here in this venue can I
get a show of hands yes all right all
right that's a lot of people already
securing their future beautiful
okay
[Music]
foreign